cute.
かわいい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
What do you think?
どうですか?
Hmm.
うーん
Does it feel good?
いい感じ?
Is that what you're counting on?
自分が当てに行っているのなんですか?
Kind of, but it's embarrassing.
なんか、でも恥ずかしい
I'm sitting in bed.
ごおぶさましてます
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
It's been a while since it came out, and it's been out for about a month and a half.
久しぶりに出て、もう1ヶ月半くらい出してますけど
I agree.
そうですね
The smile on the bottom of your face is wonderful.
顔の底の笑顔が素敵ですね
What do you think?
どうですか?
Lately, I've been like this...
最近、ちょっとこう...
Men's stuff.
男ネタとか
Nothing.
なんもない
Why is that, even though it's so cute?
なぜなんですか、こんなにかわいいのに
I wonder why I haven't had any encounters.
なんでさ、出会いがない
I'll say more.
もっと言いますよね
Well, but.
まあ、でもね
If I could find a good person, I don't think they would come to me like this.
いい人ができたら、こうやって来てくれることもないと思うので
As an uncle, I feel like it's a good thing.
おじさんとしても、よかったって感じなんですけど
So for the past month and a half.
ってことは、この1ヶ月半くらい
Are you not doing that?
そういうことはしてないんですか?
Yeah.
うん
Is it true?
本当ですか?
Actually, weren't you the only one working hard?
実は、おひとりが頑張ってたんじゃないですか?
I'm not working hard alone.
おひとりでも頑張ってないです
you must.
絶対です
Well, do you want to do that?
まあ、そういうことにしときますか?
Yeah.
うん
Thank you again for your continued support today.
今日もまたよろしくお願いします
Yes, please.
はい、お願いします
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing, it's been great for a while now.
恥ずかしいな、この間もえらくね
It felt good though.
いい感じでしたけど
Is the way you touch like an old man?
触り方がおじさん?
Yeah.
うん
Again, I'm touching her like before.
また、チョンチョンと、前みたいに触ってますけど
Kind of a soft touch.
なんか、ソフトタッチ
What is that soft touch?
なに、そのソフトタッチって
I don't know, it's kind of a soft touch.
わかんない、なんかソフトタッチ
A hard touch is fine though.
ハードタッチでもいいですけど
Hit me with a hard touch.
ハードタッチ叩いて
No, it's not.
いや、違う
It has a bit of a hard meaning to it.
ハードの意味合いが少しね
What do you think about today's uncle?
どうですか、今日のおじさんのやつは?
Well, I don't know yet.
えー、わかんない、まだ
Does that mean I have to check this thoroughly?
ということは、これはしっかり確認しないといけないんですか?
How do I check?
どうやって確認するんですか?
Please take it off.
脱いでください
So, can I have you pull this out?
じゃあ、これは引っ張ってもらってもいいですか?
pull.
引っ張る
difficult.
難しい
Maybe one piece at a time.
多分、片っ端ずつ
Ah, that's right, it's fine because it's definitely one by one.
あ、そうです、絶対ずつなのでいい
Ah, bold.
あ、大胆
Well, because.
えー、だって
What do you think?
どうですか?
Don't check.
確認しない
A little bit.
ちょっとなんか
I'm already working on my pants though.
もうパンツに手がかかってますけど
Ah, but I feel like I'm feeling a little better.
あ、でもなんか、ちょっと元気みたい
I need to check how you are doing.
どう元気か確認しないと
Somehow,
なんか、
Does it feel good?
いい 感じ?
What are we going to do after this?
これは、これのあとはどうするんですか?
After that,
のあとは、
I'm fine now.
もう 元気です
Well, there is no need for a good one.
まあ、いいのもなくていいです
from.
から
So, is it okay to wear a skirt?
じゃあ、 スカートもいいですか?
Skirt too.
スカートも
That's nice.
いいですね
A nice calming color.
ちゃんと落ち着いた色が
Is this just a blur?
これ、そのままブラーなんですか?
It seems like it's okay to see this.
これは、見えてもいいみたいな
Maybe your clothes are a little thin.
服がちょっと薄かったりとか
It's okay if you see it at that time.
その時に、見えても大丈夫ですよ
That's nice.
いいですね
It's convenient, isn't it?
便利ですよね
That's nice.
いいですね
Show me the net.
ネ ット 見せてくれ
That's nice.
いいですね
It would be better to have your brain react for a moment.
ちょっと、脳反応してもらった方がいいですから
It's too deep.
奥入れすぎる
Yes, open your mouth again.
はい、もう一回、口開けて
Yeah, somehow.
うん、なんとか
Somehow.
なんとか
I'll add more internet.
ネットもっと入れちゃいます
May I?
いいですか?
Isn't it delicious?
おいしくない?
There were a lot of them.
いっぱい出てた
Highest.
最高
Just let me wash it myself like usual.
ちょっと、いつもみたいに 普通に自分で洗ってもらってもらって
May I?
いい ですか?
There's a puddle of water.
なんか、水溜りられてる
A puddle?
水溜り?
Is it okay?
いいんですか?
It was dirty just now, though.
さっきだって汚れてたのですが
Ah, then.
ああ、じゃあ
I'm leaving.
出ます
But it might be good.
でも、いいかも
It might be good.
いいかも
After all, take it slow.
やっぱり、ゆっくり
slowly.
ゆっくり
It feels good.
いい感じです
This is a good thing.
これは、いいことですよ
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
I took a long bath earlier.
さっき、さんざんお風呂でね
Because you told me about me.
僕のことを言わしてくれたんで
Can I have that become MG?
それが、MGになってもらっていいですか?
A little further forward.
もう少し前へ
I think it would be better without the bustle.
バストルのないほうがいいかな
Do you remember?
覚えてますか?
I remember.
覚えてます
Do you want to try it yourself?
自分にしてみる?
Do you find yourself relying on it?
自分が当てに行ってるようになってますか?
That's not true.
そんなことない
amazing.
すごい
It's kind of embarrassing, but maybe the amazing one will win.
なんか、恥ずかしいけど、 すごいのほうが勝つかも
This time, you've never seen it before.
今 度、見られたことないですよね
I'll do it for a while.
ちょっと、やる
Oh no, I'm afraid.
やば、恐れてる
Because you made me feel good earlier,
さっき、 気持ちよくしてもらったから、
This time, it's me again.
今度は、私が、 もう一回
Do you remember?
覚えてますか?
Let me in.
私を、入れます